Contact

SaburoNakamoto@protonmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/saburo-nakamoto-93949b20a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React.js

Vue.js

Redux Thunk

Saburo Nakamoto

Senior Frontend Web Developer at Upwork Sakai

Summary

Senior React/Vue.JS Front-End Developer

I am a professional developer with over 7+ years of experience in web development.

I have spent most of my career in web development-starting with PHP, later working with Java and Spring, and now I am mastering the front-end field.

I love to work with great people, inspiring others, and being inspired. My specialties include JavaScript/TypeScript, Node.js, React, Vue.js, and many more.

The scope of my professional skills are below:

- Language: ECMA(ES6), JavaScript, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3,GraphQL, Sass, Java, Python
- Frameworks/Libraries:
- React: React.js, Redux-saga, React Router, GatsbyJS, Next.js
- Vue: Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify.js, Nuxt.js, Vue-Material
- Test Frameworks: Jest, React-Testing-Library, Cypress
- Database: My SQL, MongoDB, AWS DynamoDB
- Platforms: Windows, Linux, Heroku, AWS, Google Firebase
- Tools: NPM, Mocha, Git, GitHub, GitLab, Slack, WebStorm, VS Code, Trello, Jira

I'm a good team player and can follow Agile methodology to provide rapid project delivery.

Best Regards!

Experience

Upwork Senior Frontend Web Developer July 2014 - Present (6 years 9 months)

Freelancer

Junior Web Developer March 2016 - May 2020 (4 years 3 months)

- Developed an application which manages subscriptions and monthly payments.
- Developed an event management web application where the client is able to manage his events and all of the guests.
- Rewrote an Angular 2.0 application with Vue.js
- Created a custom CMS with Vue.js and AWS Lamda for a client with specail needs in functionality.

Freelancer.com
React Developer
May 2019 - January 2020 (9 months)

- Created reusable UI framework.
- Used GraphQL API.
- Reduced ton of boilerplate codes with custom hooks.

DBMS Insights Inc.

JavaScript and Front end Web Developer March 2016 - November 2016 (9 months)

- Worked with a React/Redux environment on a major enterprise product already in production.
- Helped integrate charts libraries based on D3 and React.

Education

Osaka Shiritsu Kizu Junior High School

· (2011 - 2014)

Tokyo University of Information Sciences
Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2011 - 2014)